<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>admin on Andres Ladino</title>
    <link>/authors/admin/</link>
    <description>Recent content in admin on Andres Ladino</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/authors/admin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Display Jupyter Notebooks with Academic</title>
      <link>/post/jupyter/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/jupyter/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This post was original authored by the website documentation. I have decided to leave it for documentation purposes and also for those who are curious.
from IPython.core.display import Image Image(&#39;https://www.python.org/static/community_logos/python-logo-master-v3-TM-flattened.png&#39;)  print(&amp;quot;Welcome to Academic!&amp;quot;)  Welcome to Academic!  Install Python and Jupyter Install Anaconda which includes Python 3 and Jupyter notebook.
Otherwise, for advanced users, install Jupyter notebook with pip3 install jupyter.
Create a new blog post as usual Run the following commands in your Terminal, substituting &amp;lt;MY_WEBSITE_FOLDER&amp;gt; and my-post with the file path to your Academic website folder and a name for your blog post (without spaces), respectively:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Academic: the website designer for Hugo</title>
      <link>/post/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This post was original authored by the website documentation. I have decided to leave it for documentation purposes and also for those who are curious.
Academic makes it easy to create a beautiful website for free using Markdown. Customize anything on your site with widgets, themes, and language packs.
Follow our easy step by step guide to learn how to build your own free website with Academic. Check out the personal demo or the business demo of what you&amp;rsquo;ll get in less than 10 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/author/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/author/admin/</guid>
      <description>I am a postdoctoral researcher in Automatic Control at the IFSTTAR Laboratory. My recent research interests include Networked Control Systems (NCS), Cyberphysical Systems (CPS), Intelligent Transportation Systems (ITS) and Artificial Intelligence (AI). Previously, I did my PhD at INRIA/CNRS with the NeCS team in development of Short-term Forecasting and estimation techniques for traffic variables. Currently, I work at LICIT group working on control techniques for connected and automated vehicles (CAV)s, in this team I develop traffic flow models, and traffic simulation algorithms for truck platoon strategies.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>